One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Remnants
Kalıntılar
Got it, Perospero?
Anladın mı Perospero?
Entering an alliance with Kaido was my decision.
İttifak fikrine ben karar verdim.
Be that as it may,
Öyle olsa bile...
your family has long dreamed of the day that you become the Pirate King, Mama!
ailece daima senin korsanlar kralı olmanın hayalini kurduk.
Lick!
perorin!
I know that, of course.
Farkındayım.
Can't you all just trust me on this?
Bana itimatınız yok mu?
Okay...
Tamam,
Well, that's a relief.
içim rahatladı.
I see.
Anlıyorum.
I suppose this means our ogre-hunting party has officially disbanded, Perospero?
Öyleyse şeytan avı işi iptal, Perospero.
Even though I accepted your offer.
Teklif eden de sendin.
Marco!
Marco!
I can't believe you're helping those punks.
Çoluk çocukla iş tuttuğuna inanamıyorum!
I thought better of you.
Senden daha iyisini beklerdim.
The remnants of Whitebeard's crew must truly be lost without their captain.
Beyazsakal kalıntıları ne yapacağını şaşırmış.
I don't think you know what "remnant" truly means, Big Mom!
"Kalıntı" ne demek, bir sözlüğe bak istersen Big Mom.
Do you really think...
Gerçekten hâlâ...
we're still bound to Pops' will?
Babalığın iradesine bağlı olduğumuzu mu düşünüyorsun?
Those of us left behind...
Biz kalanlar...
are free!
özgürüz-yoi!
True... dead men give no orders.
Doğru, ölü bir adamdan emir alacak hâliniz yok.
You're free to act out.
Canın ne istiyorsa onu yap.
That's not quite it...
Çarpıtmasaydın iyiydi.
I'm free to do whatever I want!
Fakat istediğimi yapmakta özgürüm!
I knew it was him!
Cidden burada!
Carrot! Where are you going?!
Carrot, nereye gidiyorsun?
He was there! Pedro's killer!
Pedro'nun öcünü almaya!
Now's your chance, Straw Hat! Go!
Hasır Şapka-san, fırsat varken gidin!
Thanks!
Sağ ol!
Banquet Hall Inside the Castle
Ziyafet Salonu Kalenin İçi
The whole island is in chaos.
Adada kıyamet kopuyor.
Are they gonna come all the way up here?
Buraya da gelirler mi acaba?
I can't believe no one's here in the tatami room!
Kimsecikler kalmadı şurada ya!
Would you sing us a song, Big Sis Maria?
Maria abla, bize bir şarkı söyler misiniz?
All right.
Peki.
How about this?
Böyle bir şey olur mu?
♪ On a snowy night... ♪
♪ Karlı bir gecede...
Wait!
Bekle!
♪ ...two yearning lovers... ♪
...yanıp tutuşsalar da...
♪ kept apart by fate... ♪
uzun zamandır...
♪ kept apart by circumstance... ♪
birbirine kavuşamayan aşıklar...
♪ will finally meet again! ♪
nihayet kavuşacaklar! ♪
♪ Under the moonlight... ♪
♪ Ay ışığının altında...
So romantic!
Ne romantik.
♪ ...their passion... ♪
...tutkularıyla...
♪ burning! ♪
küle dönecekler! ♪
Master Kin!
Kin-sama!
Kin!
Kin-san!
I will avenge Lord Oden!
Efendimizin öcü için!
Take this!
Geber!
You really wanna die that badly?
Eceline mi susadın?
Kin!
Kin-san!
What?!
Ne?
You guys are not Oden after all.
Siz Oden'in tırnağı olamazsınız.
Pretending to be great samurai from the safety of Oden's shadow,
Oden'in kanatları altında büyük samuraylar gibi geçiniyordunuz.
and even now, after his death, you still play at being samurai.
Oden'in vefatından sonra bile samuraycılık oynayanların elinden...
What can you do?
ne gelebilir ki?
If you think we're just playing at being samurai, why not fight us and find out?!
Samuraycılık mı oynuyoruz, vücudunda test edelim o hâlde!
All right... Bring it on!
Gelin de alın başını!
Attack!
Hücum!
Crimson Cat Dance!
Kızıl Kedi Dansı!
Kappa Style...
Kappa Stili:
Celestial Torrent!
Deniz Nehri!
What?!
Ne?
Canine Scourge!
Köpek Azabı!
Lingering Snow Scythes!
Kar Tırpanı Yağışı!
Slicing Rounds!
Keskin Çemberler!
What's this?!
Nasıl iş bu?
Their attacks aren't even close to the level of Oden's swordplay.
Oden'in stilini kullanmadıkları hâlde...
How can they cut me?!
nasıl beni kesebiliyorlar?
Kaido!
Kaido!
Do it!
Gel hadi!
I said, do it!
Gel hadi dedim!
Ninpo: Scroll-Scroll Technique!
Ninpo: Parşömen Tekniği!
My scroll will roll up anything!
Parşömenlerim her şeyi sarmalayabilir.
And now, I return it to you...
Şimdi de iade ediyorum.
Blast Breath...
Sıcak Nefes...
Restoration!
Yenilen!
So you want to kill me?
Beni öldürebileceğinizi mi sandınız?
You're just a bunch of cowardly retainers...
Sizler, efendinizin gölgesini kovalayan...
chasing your Lord Oden's phantom!
bir avuç ezik hizmetkârsınız!
He is right.
Evet.
We have always been cowards.
Eziktik.
I shall teach you how to use the Oden two-sword style!
Size Oden İki Kılıç Stili'ni göstereceğim!
No thank you.
İyi böyle.
We possess our own style...
Hepimizin kendi stili var.
But why?! This is the Oden two-sword style!
Neden be? Oden İki Kılıç Stili bu!
Do you not want to inherit it?!
Neden miras almak istemiyorsunuz?
Of course we wanted to inherit it.
Elbette çok istiyorduk.
Everyone insisted they were his first disciple.
Herkes gözde öğrenci olmaya takmış durumdaydı.
There was a serious fight to determine who was his first student.
Gözde öğrenci olmak için savaşa bile tutuştuk.
We all loved Oden so much, it looked like a fight to the death.
Hepimiz onu çok sevdiğimizden birbirimizi öldürmeye bile niyetlendik.
– Oden...
– Oden...
– Two-Sword Style!
– ...İki Kılıç Stili!
Is this your idea of a joke?
N'apıyorsunuz?
Such pathetic imitations!
Boş hareketler!
Listen, guys!
İyi dinleyin!
Ryuo is...
Ryuo...
Listen to me!
Dinlesenize be!
We have honed our skills with the blade, all for this day when we save Wano!
Wano'yu bugün kurtarabilmek adına kılıç becerilerimizi ilerlettik!
Flame-Rend!
Alev Yaran!
Do not underestimate... my samurai!
Samuraylarımı hafife alayım deme!
People will remember your heroic death for generations.
Senin bu yiğitçe vedan asırlar boyu unutulmayacak.
They can forget me for all I care!
Unutulmam umurumda değil!
My spirit will live on!
Ruhum yaşamaya devam edecek!
– Oden Two-Sword Style:
– Oden İki Kılıç Stili:
– Halcyon Totsuka!
– ...Cennet Totsuka!
Hal
Cen
Halcyon
Cennet
Totsu
Totsu
Totsuka
Totsuka
Flower Capital
Çiçek Başkenti
Sing! Dance!
Şarkı söyleyin! Dans edin!
Be merry! For today is the Fire Festival!
Vur patlasın çal oynasın, bugün Ateş Festivali!
The Flower Capital is the lone place that flourishes in Wano.
Wano'nun refahı yüksek yegane yeri Çiçek Başkenti'dir.
However, like the rest of the country, its population hides terror and tension
Burada oturanlar bile tıpkı ülkenin geri kalanı gibi...
behind a thin veneer of frivolity.
korkularını gülümsemeyle gizleyip hayatta kalmaya çalışıyorlar.
"Someday, the Kozuki samurai will save this country."
Bunun nedeni ise, Kozuki samuraylarının günün birinde ülkeyi kurtaracak olması.
They could carry on...
Herkes bu efsaneye...
because they all believed in such a seemingly true legend.
gönülden inanmakta çünkü.
Delicious!
Çok iyi be!
That really hits the spot!
Bütün gün içebilirim!
The Fire Festival sure is fun...
Ateş Festivali ne güzel.
Yes...
Evet...
It takes me back to the good old days.
Beni eski güzel günlere götürüyor.
I wish today would go on just like this...
Keşke bugün hiç bitmese...
forever and ever...
ve böyle sürüp gitse...
So tasty!
Bayıldım.
We get to drink such clean water.
Böyle temiz bir su içebiliyoruz.
What a luxury!
Ne güzel bir gün!
The air is so fresh...
Hava da temiz.
Let's really take it in.
Bir güzel içimize çekelim.
Once the festival ends, it's back to sobriety...
Festivalle beraber içki faslı da bitecek.
for a whole 'nother year!
Yine koca bir yıl bekleyeceğiz.
Dammit!
Böyle işe!
If only Orochi wasn't backed by Kaido!
Keşke Orochi, Kaido'nun desteğine sahip olmasaydı!
No one's gonna get killed today.
Bugün kimse öldürülmeyecek.
What a wonderful day!
Şahane bir gün.
Orochi will be back tomorrow, though!
Orochi yarın burada olacak gerçi.
I bet the Kozuki Clan is fighting them right now!
Kozuki Hanesi savaşa girmiştir şimdi!
Oh, that's interesting, even if it's complete horseshit!
Hayali bile güzel.
Tell me more!
Devam etsene.
Alright then! They've brought back warriors from all over the world,
Peki! Dört bir yandan Onigashima'ya adam yığıp...
and they're at Onigashima right now, slicing up Orochi and Kaido and creating chaos!
Orochi'yle Kaido'yu sırayla kesmiş ve ortalığın anasını ağlatıyorlar!
Keep going! Keep going!
Devam! Devam!
Today's the day to share wild fantasies!
Bugün hayallerimizi paylaşma günü!
S-So cold...!
D-Donuyorum!
Help me!
Yardım edin!
This is bad...
Vaziyet sakat.
Stay away from them!
Onlara yaklaşmayın!
Fall back!
Geri çekilin!
Get away from them!
Onlardan uzak durun!
The samurai are splitting up... Why?
Samuraylar birbiriyle savaşıyor. N'oluyor?
This must be that plague of his...
Şu vebadan olsa gerek...
You'll turn into an ogre just by touching them.
Dokunsan şeytana dönüşüyorsun.
It's highly contagious...
Korkutucu bir bulaşma hızı.
How could he spread such a virus?
Böyle bir virüsü nasıl yayar?
He's the real ogre here!
Şeytanın ta kendisi!
Seal off the exits to the other floors!
Diğer katlara giden yolları kapatın.
This floor is done for!
Bu kat iflah olmaz artık.
This is my masterpiece!
Başyapıtım be.
Plague rounds:
Veba mermileri:
Ice Ogre!
Buz Şeytanı!
1st Basement Level Inside the Castle
1. Bodrum Katı Kalenin İçi
Outta my way!
Çekilin!
You damn cockroach!
Seni piç!
I said "Outta my way"!
Çekilin demedim mi?
Wait, Luffy!
Bekle, Luffy.
What are you doing?!
Ne yapıyorsun be?
You're gonna fight Kaido, right?
Sen Kaido'yla dövüşeceksin.
Save your energy for now!
Enerjini korumaya bak.
Off with Straw Hat's head!
Hasır Şapka'nın kellesini uçurun!
Outta the way, swirly brows!
Sen karışma, kıvrık kaş!
Let's do it!
İndirelim şunu!
I can handle all of you brutes by myself!
Size ben tek yeterim.
Party Table Kick Course!
Parti Masası Tekme Servisi!
Damn you!
İtin tohumu,
How dare you do that to my men?!
adamlarımı haşat edersin ha!
You're not getting past me!
Buradan geçiş yok!
Prepare yourself!
Hazırlayın kendinizi!
Headliner Briscola Gorilla Smile Fruit Beast Pirates
Öncü Briscola Goril Gülücük Meyvesi Canavar Korsanları
Why's the gorilla growing from there?! It's weird!
Goril elinde mi çıkıyo'? Çok garip!
Is that so?!
Çok biliyorsun.
Then how exactly should a gorilla...
O zaman bir gorilin nereden çıkacağını...
grow out of someone?!
göstersene bana!
How would I know?!
Ne bileyim lan ben?
Gorilla Punch Punch!
Goril Yumruğumun Yumruğu!
Wow!
Vay be.
He's tougher than he looks!
Güçlüymüş.
That Gorilla Punch is so cool!
Goril Yumruğu süpermiş!
Water Shot!
Su Atışı!
Oh! Jinbe!
Oo! Jinbe!
I thought I would find you around here.
Seni burada bir yerde bulabileceğimi düşündüm.
Looks like I was right...
Haklı da çıktım.
Briscola!
Briscola-san!
Are you all right?
İyi misiniz?
Ow, ow, ow...
Of, ay, ay...
Hey! Are you okay?!
Hey, iyi misin?
Stay with me!
Topla kendini!
Hey, you!
Lan ibiş!
How dare you attack us!
Erkek adam arkadan saldırır mı?
Alright! It's my turn now!
Tamam, bu sefer ben dövüşeceğim!
Come on! How many times do I have to tell you to save your energy?!
Yavaş! 50 kere dedim enerjini koru diye.
You'll take too long beating up this many guys!
Bu kadar adamı halletmen uzun sürer!
Shut up!
Kes!
I'll polish them off in ten seconds!
10 saniyede icaplarına bakarım.
Any complaints?
Tamam mı?
Yeah! It'd only take three seconds if I was there!
Tamam değil! Ben yardım edersem üç saniye sürer.
Hey, stop ignoring me!
Beni siklemiyorlar!
Prepare yourselves!
Hazır olun!
Gorilla Punch Punch!
Goril Yumruğumun Yumruğu!
Fishman Karate: Shark Tile Fist!
Balıkadam Karatesi: Köpek Balığı Tuğla Yumruğu!
Briscola!
Briscola-san!
Oh, nice one!
Vay, helal.
You're awesome, Jinbe!
Süpersin Jinbe!
Luffy!
Luffy!
I'll escort you to the rooftop!
Sana çatıya kadar eşlik edeceğim.
You need to save your energy for now!
Sen enerjini koru.
Why are you taking control?!
Niye idareyi sen alıyorsun?
I've already taken Luffy this far!
Luffy'yi buraya kadar getiren benim.
I see. My apologies!
Haklısın. Kusuruma bakma.
Luffy! Our samurai allies should be up there already!
Luffy, şimdiye müttefikimiz olan samuraylar varmıştır.
Let's meet up with them!
Onlarla buluşalım!
Alright! Got it!
Tamam, olur!
How the hell are you so on top of everything?
Durumu okuması da iyi adamın!
How dare you take down Briscola?!
Briscola-san'ı yere yığdılar!
Get them!
Haklayın şunları!
Look... Luffy will jump at any opportunity to fight.
Luffy dövüş fırsatını kaçırmaz, ona göre.
Let's keep on our toes then!
Göz kulak olalım.
Onigashima
Onigashima
Right-Brain Tower
Sağ Beyin Kulesi
Wait!
Dursana be!
What's the situation, Bao Huang?
Durum ne, Bao Huang?
Right, so, Yamato and Momonosuke are headed outside through the Right-Brain Tower!
Yamato'yla Momonosuke, Sağ Beyin Kulesi'nden çıkışa doğru ilerliyor.
That's good enough.
Yeterli.
This is King.
Ben King.
We've ascertained the identities of the idiots who crashed the banquet.
Ziyafete sızan dingiller kimmiş öğrendim.
The enemy's army numbers around 5,400.
Düşmanın 5.400 adamı var.
The majority are samurai, led by Oden's retainers.
Çoğu samuray ve Oden'in hizmetkârlarının emrindeler.
It would seem...
Özetle...
the Kozuki Clan has staked its prestige...
Kozuki Hanesi tekrar güç kazanmak için...
in an attempt to restore their name.
milleti ayaklandı.
They want to make Oden's son, Kozuki Momonosuke, the shogun of Wano.
Niyetleri Oden'in oğlu Kozuki Momonosuke'yi Wano şogunu yapmak.
To all available Gifters and Soaring Six members...
Boşta olan tüm Yetenekliler ve...
my orders are as follows:
Tobi Roppo üyelerine emrimdir:
Kill Kozuki Momonosuke, who is currently escaping through the Right-Brain Tower,
Şu an Sağ Beyin Kulesi'nden kaçmaya çalışan Kozuki Momonosuke'yi öldürün...
and bring me his head!
ve kellesini önüme atın!
This will destroy the samurai's morale.
Bu hareket, samurayların mücadele azmine gem vurur.
Of course, I know the pirates are another matter altogether.
Korsanlar başka bir mesele tabii.
Our orders are to kill him, not to bring him in...
Onu sağ yakalamakla mükellef değiliz...
That makes things easier.
Böylesi daha kolay.
Shoot.
Ateş!
Armored Division Beast Pirates
Zırhlı Birlik Canavar Korsanları
Fetch me his corpse!
Cesedini getirin!
– Yes, sir!
– Başüstüne!
Here it is.
İşte burada.
Huh? What's this?
Heh, bu ne lan?
A barrel?
Fıçı mı?
The Armored Division's defenses cannot be broken by such a weapon!
Böyle bir silahla, biz zırhlı birliğin savunmasını yıkamazsın!
Shinobu!
Shinobu!
You mustn't!
Aman!
Please stay hidden!
Saklanın siz!
Nice try!
Olmadı be.
Every member of our squad has an armored body.
Nerede vücudu sağlam olan adam varsa benim ekipte.
There's no way out!
Kaçacak yeriniz kalmadı!
Aim for the kid!
Velede nişan alın!
Lord Momonosuke!
Momonosuke-sama!
Please... run...
Siz... kaçın!
Shinobu...
Shinobu...
I'll kill you...
Seni de o veletle...
along with the brat!
öteki tarafa yollayacağım!
You can't even shield him!
Sen ona kalkan bile olamazsın!
Shinobu!
Shinobu!
Ru...
Ka...
Run, Lord Momonosuke!
Kaçın, Momonosuke-sama!
Run?
Kaçayım mı?
Is that what a shogun is supposed to do?
Şogunlar böyle mi yapar?
Shinobu! Shinobu!
Shinobu! Shinobu!
You're mine!
Elimdesin!
I beg you...!
N'olur yapma!
I beg you!
N'olur!
Well, well...
Bak sen...
Are you sure you want to interfere,
Karışmak mı istiyorsunuz...
Young Master Yamato?
Genç Efendi Yamato.
I'm not interfering.
Karışmayacağım.
I'm here to fight for the Kozuki.
Kozuki adına savaşacağım.
For I... am Oden!
Ben, Oden'im çünkü!
Cut his throat!
Boğazını kesin!
We haven't won until we've removed his head from his neck!
Kellesini alana kadar bu iş bitmiş sayılmaz!
You are right!
Doğru diyorsun!
Sever Kaido's windpipe!
Kaido'nun işini bitirin!
Within your spirit, I saw the shadow of Kozuki Oden...
Gösterdiğiniz azimde Kozuki Oden'in gölgesini gördüm.
It wouldn't have been a bad death...
Ölüp gideydim keşke.
Every time this scar aches,
Yaram her sızladığında...
I remember that fateful day...
o gün aklıma geliyor.
Help!
Yardım et!
Father!
Baba!
Father, save me!
Baba, kurtar beni!
Guess who!
Yanıldın!
If only no one had interfered at that exact moment...
Ah bi' karışmasalardı...
But you guys are not Oden after all...
Ama siz Oden'in kalibresinde değilsiniz.
There will never be another monstrous samurai like him!
Öyle deli kuvvetli bir samuray bir daha gelmez.
It's too shallow!
Yetersiz!
You aren't even strong enough to reopen the old scar!
Siz o gün aldığım yarayı bile tekrar açamazsınız!
None of you are!
Sizin boyunuzu aşar.
Invisible slashes?!
Görünmez kesişler mi?!
– Kiku!
– Kiku!